[{"answer": "I think personally what Ann's probably going through is she is determined to show up for work every day, do the great job that she always has been.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "What are your feelings about what's been happening?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think you can lay the blame squarely on Ann's shoulders, although that certainly seems to be what's happening.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Why hasn't it worked?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well, if it's his fault, he's not losing his job so I don't think anybody would agree with him when he says that.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "I mean would it have been fairer to say, as he has said, look, it may be my fault?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Well, I think, you know, whatever problems, that's the trouble.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Is she the answer, do you think, to whatever problems the \"Today\" show may have?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Well, that's truly going to be a decision to be made by the judge or by the jury when they look at this case because the whole issue is whether or not he had reasonable fear of great bodily injuries.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Do you believe that the video proves that he had injuries consistent with a life or death battle?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Well, I understand his position.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "Do you accept that?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "I would have to be -- it would be pure conjecture on my part.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "What has been happening to him behind the scenes?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Well, when I -- I think I shared with you when I was the non-lawyer in this case before I was involved in it and heard about the facts leading up to it, and then heard about the charge of second degree, and having had a lot of second degree murder cases, I was curious to see where evidence of second degree would come from.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "ORGAN: Do you feel instinctively, when you heard that it was a murder charge, did you feel that the real debate, or to be over a manslaughter charge, that whatever it was, it wasn't murder?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "I believe under the law and the case law that he is entitled to a bond.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Do you expect George Zimmerman to be granted bond?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "I'm well.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "One of the reasons I chose to write the book was to help me with my personal recovery.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "And how cathartic, if it has been, was writing the book?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "You know, she was troubled with -- with those demons for a long time.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Would you think that's a fair assessment, that she just in the end was undone by those demons?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Well, you left a little bit out there.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Quite ironic, isn't it?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Well, I can't say on air.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 331, "question": "What's the bit I left out?", "qSentId": 330}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Has he ever contacted you, written to you, called you?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "We were -- we were in L.A. for the Grammys.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "But when you heard what happened to Whitney Houston, what went through your mind?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "It's difficult to say, Piers.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Tell me this, from what you saw happen to your girl and from what happening to Whitney, Michael Jackson, to a certain degree, and so on, the pressures of being a hugely successful musical star in the modern era, do they bring a very particular stress, do you think?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "You know, really, the book came about from years of meeting people along my journey and really hearing from other people their stories of loss and difficulty, and finding that, you know, maybe my story could be helpful to others, so that was really what prompted me to write the book.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Why did you feel this was the time to do the book?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "He was, you know, one of those people who just really stood out.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "What kind of guy was he?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "I think after 9/11, like a lot of people, Pat really sort of took a step back and reprioritized what was important to him in his life.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Why did he feel so strongly, do you think, that he had to do that?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "It's a difficult thing for families, you know.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "What were you thinking?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "No, I didn't try to persuade him not to.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Did you try and persuade him not to, to start with?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "I think that's the difficult part, is there is no one answer for everyone.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "What advice do you give so many other war widows, girlfriends, wives?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "It just made me question everything that we had been told.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "How did that make you feel?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Certainly there was a mix of emotions, and anger being one of them, confusion, and just, you know, betrayal.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "You must have felt angry, didn't you, that possibly you'd been deliberately lied to?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "You know, I'm not sure.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "How high do you think it went, the deceit?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Well, when I originally read it, it was something that was very difficult because at that time I didn't want to live.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "When you read that, what went through your mind?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know if that's why he wrote it or if it was just something that he felt like he wanted to leave something comforting and -- and to be able to say, you know, this is what I wish for you if I don't return.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Do you think he would have instinctively second-guessed how you would feel in that scenario?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "It was just a really difficult experience to be there and to sit in the back of the room and listen to all of this play out.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "You say in the book that while Rumsfeld was testifying, you say every fiber in my body was crying B.S. Why did you feel that so strongly?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "You know, it's been actually quite a while since I've seen a lot of that and really sort of relived it.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "Eight years later, do you feel any closer to knowing exactly what happened or not?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "It was a long journey.", "docId": "120626pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "How hard was it to make that move?", "qSentId": 568}]